chat gp4 is free now the version that
they used to charge us 20 bucks a month
for you can cancel that you don't need
to pay for it you get access to 80
messages every 3 hours of chat GPT 40
which stands for chat gp4 Omni but it's
the best algorithm for AI that you can
use for your marketing as well as
brainstorming and learning what I'm
going to show you is by the end of this
video how to use AI to help you grow
your business to help you make more
money to learn new things and what my
best strategies are for using artificial
intelligence I'm going to give you a
crash course if you're brand new you've
never used AI before that's what this
video is now they've done research about
75% of all adults are using AI in some
capacity truth is social media
algorithms if you're watching this on
YouTube or Facebook or you have a
Netflix account we're using AI the
Netflix algorithm literally uses AI to
figure out okay how far do you watch
into a movie and it tells you what to
what recommendations are the Facebook
and Instagram news feeds they pay
attention to how much you're consuming
content where are you commenting if you
scroll on social media and you pause on
a video and you watch it the algorithm
there's a computer that makes a note
that you did that and I'm convinced they
might even be looking through the camera
to see how your face is responding to it
that's a little creepy however maybe
they're not who knows there's no proof
of that
however they are using as much data as
possible to to figure out what to show
you and this can trigger your mood and
things like this that's a whole other
conversation how the algorithm is
literally controlling a lot of the way
that Society thinks and there's a lot of
evidence for this and they can deny it
all they want but if you actually
understand how the technology works the
reason these companies are in business
is to be able to control where people
are looking and the output different
than traditional media where you would
watch a TV show and would be on at one
time they can show different things to
different people that's personalized
based on your desires and what you're
actually looking for all that to say
we're not going to be talking about that
that's way more advanced computer
science stuff we're going to just be
talking about how you can use Ai and the
free version of chat GPT to do a lot of
really really cool things in your life
you can learn things it's literally like
having access to the infinite amount of
libraries that are out there the
information is very accurate now as far
as compared to before and how you can
fact check things as well and certain
resources to truly tell if the
information that it gives you is good or
not we've used it for marketing the AI
underlying algorithms of these since
2021 you might be saying chat gbt only
only came out in 2022 well in March of
2021 there's actually a company that I
signed up for that had an AI they used
version three this was before this was
like two versions back of chat GPT they
used version three before it was called
chat GPT it was just called
gpt3 and then they created an app that
was on top of this and it helped write
your Facebook ads and your marketing
campaigns and I learned because I was
experimenting with it that if I talk to
it like a person it would respond to me
like another human and I was starting to
do a lot of the chat things people were
doing with chat GPT to find information
as a quote unquote off label use case
even though it was an app that was
supposed to help you with your Facebook
ads I started asking it for information
about various topics and things like
this that I wanted to learn and it gave
me things that they didn't sell the
product to do but it was able to do that
and so I learned 3 years ago how to use
it the way that I do today I use it as
well to help me with my mental health I
use it to solve problems I use it if I'm
stuck if I'm in the middle of even
coaching a client or I'm working with a
client I say okay this is a great
question let's ask a couple different
ways in chat GPT and let's see what we
can come up with and it will help
brainstorm ideas now here's one thing we
don't want we don't want AI to replace
human connection okay that's the number
one thing we don't want computers
controlling us we don't want to become
enslaved to computer overlords the
problem is this is that often times if
you're even using social media
algorithms people are so hooked on these
that it's almost like they can't stop
using them and to be honest many of us
are dependent and codependent with AI
algorithms already in our everyday life
it's better to figure out how to
activate your brain brain to think on
its own and then how to use these
algorithms to serve you and to help you
and so what I'm going to show you is
this if you don't have an account go to
to chat gp.com and create a free account
it just takes a couple of seconds to do
and the version that you have might look
a little bit different than the one that
we have here but you'll notice that it
says chat GPT in the corner and then
when you ask it something you know hi
there my name is Jeremiah let's
chat hey Jeremiah great to meet you what
would you like to chat about today and
look I can even turn on voices hi
Jeremiah it's great to meet you what
would you like to chat about today I can
even change what the voices are and how
it communicates with me I can change
which voice it it uses I like breeze
let's do Breeze hi Jeremiah it's great
to meet you what would you like to chat
about today perfect this is awesome so I
can say this I can say um and I actually
have something on my computer here where
I can uh talk right into the microphone
do I have this open no I don't
okay I'm here with some people showing
them how this works and by the way you
notice I didn't spell that
right but it still got it that's great
Jeremiah I'm here to help with any
questions or demonstrate how things work
what would you in your group like to
know or
see what are some of the ways
people can use chat GPT
40 in their everyday life or business
especially if they want to start a
coaching or mentoring
business there are many ways that people
can use it you can use it as a personal
assistant manage appointments and
reminders do research writing assistant
draft emails and letters you can help it
with studying understanding concepts
skill development you can help it
generate meal plans for you workout
routines health and fitness mindfulness
exercise stress relief techniques it can
help with client interaction feedback
collection with clients it can help you
write blog posts social media posts
develop curriculum worksheets and
training materials it can help you with
a number of different things in your
business from engaging with potential
clients with personalized
messages and so these are many of the
different ways that we can use AI to do
this in our in our businesses one of the
thing is is that you want to talk to it
like it's a normal
person okay great let's let's get
started let's come up with a plan for
helping me sleep more when I'm
busy creating a plan so you can sleep
more when you're busy uh addresses
various aspects of Lifestyle environment
track your sleep set a bedtime and wake
up routine gradual adjustments have a
wind down limit screen time cool
environment comfortable bedding delegate
tasks and so then I might say I have so
much to do in my business and I'm a new
dad dad with a pregnant
wife
stress stress is a big thing I always
run out of time okay so based on this
what we're able to do is we're able to
truly start to dive deeper into how the
AI can help us even develop a plan and
the routine for my life let's create a
to-do list let's do some time blocking
let's set some realistic goals Del
delegate tasks work hours eliminate
distractions and I found that deep
breathing exercises and mindfulness
techniques really help me in my life in
my business can you um expand upon this
so I copied and pasted it describe in
detail
protocol okay here's a detailed protocol
for Stress Management maybe a morning
meditation find a quiet space you're
comfortable won't be disturbed set a
timer for 15 minutes uh find a
comfortable
position focus on your breath by the way
that's exactly what I do is focus on my
breath I do this a couple times a
day breathing sensation if your mind
wanders bring your focus back to the
breath without judgment and sometimes
I'll take mindfulness breaks where I do
this and I pay attention
to what are things that come to mind as
well while I'm doing things like that
here's another great one incorporating
physical activity going for short walks
I do that evening
strolls uh strength training two to
three times a week I need to do more of
that morning breathing strength training
mindfulness yeah I mean as I've been
doing this I just went for a nice swim
that exercised my body quite a bit
before I did this video and it
invigorated my mind as far as this goes
I should have told the AI that I just
went for a swim that inv invigorated my
body before we started talking I'm
actually recording our session right now
to put on
YouTube that's wonderful swimming is
great here's a brief outline of what
we've discussed so far uh briefly
introduce the purpose of the video talk
about what we can do managing stress and
workload so again that's not the purpose
of what this video is
about um the purpose of the video is I
want to give examples to people of of
how to use AI in their business and
everyday life and our conversation is an
example of this got any other example
ideas we can show them look at this now
this is where it's going to get fun is
is going to start to brainstorm some
ideas how to handle customer service how
to do content creation sales and
marketing email management personal
assistant learning Fitness plans dietary
advice uh show a typical customer
question and have it answer it provide
different topics and
structure uh again posing a question to
chat GPT here's a question somebody
asked me recently
is here's a client question someone
asked and I do this all the time with
client questions
someone asked act as an expert in the
above field by the way to answer moving
forward so what I'm doing is I'm telling
the AI to start to act as an expert in
this field it'll respond as if it's that
way in incorporating AI in business in
everyday life so I'm all over the place
let's see client asked I'm all over the
place with my
time and focus and need to get more on
track with how I focus throughout the
day and keep track of my time to be more
productive got any any tips and so this
might be something that I could then go
in and literally uh give to this person
as far as this goes that they could use
you can use it uh you can um track your
time you can set up a dedicated
workspace limit social media work in
intervals 25 minutes with 5 minute
breaks
delegate and
Outsource um using AI you could have you
know various it can help you develop a
routine like this that might work you
can adjust the routine things like that
so as far as that goes so that's a great
way to kind of help you in your life
what
about for sales and
marketing here's some strategies for
sales and marketing uh analyze web
traffic social media and identify
potential leads PR predictive
analysis um it can come up with
personalized email
campaigns based on a client that needs
to learn what we've been discussing
above can you write a social media post
that we might be able to use based
around this info this will be
interesting so it's going to write us up
a social media post possibly that we
that we might be able to use for this
and what we're doing is this is what I
call playing with AI this is what I call
just having fun with artificial
intelligence just kind of coming up with
different ideas as far as this goes we
might not use any of what it's producing
right now but what we're doing is we're
having a conversation just like we're
going back and forth with a human or a
or a or a personal assistant or a junior
assistant one of the biggest strategies
that I used to do with clients they used
to hire me for this specifically is they
would talk back and forth with me and I
would come up with ideas that we could
do and then I started incorporating AI
where it was like me and the AI and in
fact my clients when they pay me to
consult them that's exactly what I do
they all know I got the AI in front of
me and I'm asking it questions while I'm
brainstorming things and we're working
together to come up with ideas as far as
that goes because I can be really quick
with doing that for that okay and it's
not just AI ideas it's my own brain
that's coming up with a lot of these
ideas let's do this um someone wants to
know how to use AI to grow their
business can you make a post with some
strategies
about this okay we're asking it to do
this and I'm going back and forth with
this because I want to get to a certain
stage or place with what it's creating
where we're going to start to get
specific with it one of the things that
you're noticing is a lot of the stuff
that the AI is creating it's very um it
has a lot of information okay so when it
comes to sales and marketing when it
comes to your business when it comes to
you creating content you want to start
to get more specific we want to pick
maybe some of the top ideas that stand
out to us and so this is one of the
reasons why I actually practice
mindfulness often is to calm my mind and
my body down that's one of the reason
why I went swimming is so that I can
intuitively recognize what are the most
important things to use what happens for
me and this is just for myself as I'm
reading this artificial intelligence in
my subconscious mind certain words
almost like 3D stand out on the on the
on the page they pop out to me as I'm
looking at this and that's where I start
to go in different directions based on
how my reticular activating system is
working okay can you talk about how when
I'm reading your ideas above two one to
two of the ideas sort of pop out
like 3D to me and my Ras is noticing
them intuitively as more important than
others and how this works and
how other people can do the same
themselves this will be very interesting
if you ever wanted wondered how that is
here's a social media post harness the
power of AI you're looking to grow your
business okay this is funny uh no no I
want you so I paused it because it
didn't understand what I'm
saying now shift and act as an expert in
the following prompt and answer
it okay so I'm telling it to shift into
a different
direction of an of a different prompt as
far as that goes understanding the
RAS selective attention and so the way
that it pops out orar significant to you
is the result of the reticular
activating system it's a network of
neurons that play a crucial role in
regulating wakefulness and attention and
so what it is is I'm prioritizing based
on relevance I set a clear goal to
leverage it and then what I start doing
is I start noticing certain things in a
focused environment that stand out to me
as far as that
goes how is it though that
intuitively words almost pop out of the
page or screen I'm really curious about
this side of it this phenomenon is an as
part of the intricate workings of the
RIS and the way that the that the brain
works it's filtering information it acts
as a sensory gatekeeper allowing certain
stimuli to reach the Consciousness
better and it prioritizes what is
relevant so the brain is sorting what is
relevant the way that they pop out is I
have a predetermined predefined set of
goals and interests as far as that goes
and So based on that what I'm able to do
is because I've aligned that in our
conversation things are starting to
starting to pop out of the screen and
I'm starting to get contextual cues
based on what I'm seeing I'm setting
clear intention before I'm reading
that's what we did for the last like 10
minutes we've set a clear intention for
what we're looking for with the AI and
so that's one of the ways to use AI is
you can use it to actually tune your
reticular activating system to start to
notice things and to start to fire in
certain ways and so what you're doing is
you're actually priming it's exactly
what it is you're priming your Ras to
look for different information that
supports your objectives and then I'm
engaging with the material and it starts
to stand out to me it's a fascinating
interplay between the way my brain
processes things as well as helps me set
goals and intentions and it improves my
productivity because I only kind of pay
attention to what pops out in any given
moment in time as far as that goes okay
so these are some like great strategies
to use this to optimize how you use your
brain you might have just learned
something right now even literally from
the AI and and this is by the way let's
let's look at this some of you might is
there scientific evidence for that show
me some true hard fact scientific
evidence I can I can find on
this okay searching the web it's
actually going to search the internet
and find us some websites the phenomenon
is right here selective attention and
Ras neuroc correlates of attention
neuroimaging it shows different parts of
the prefontal cortex so literally we
almost as if they're popping out right
here there's literally a uh articles
about this that are written in
Neuroscience journals about how things
become more Vivid and they stand out let
me look at this okay so the word pop out
isn't in there but it says this heighten
neural activity creates certain stimuli
to harness this
mechanism looking deeper into it so
that's really really cool is you can
even start to cite it it starts to
Google it or it uses Bing and starts to
find answers for things and you get
access to this for free using the free
version of chat GPT now let's
say I
want to make a simple
fourth grade reading
level um blog post I like to start with
a blog post about all the info about the
raas above with cited
sources understanding it have you ever
noticed how some words seem to pop off
the page when you're reading them what
is it it's neurons located in your brain
stem helps you focus on certain things
highlights information emotional
connections that's the other thing too
yes using visual aids
yep perfect okay now can you translate
this to a simple Facebook
post watch this and this might be
something that I might post a little bit
later on my social
media unlock your brain's hidden power
ever wondered why some words seem to pop
out of the page when you're reading it's
all thanks to the special part of the
brain called a reticular activating
system selective attention set clear
goals perfect generate generate
me an image or photo that illustrates
the above now this is really cool is it
can go to work and start to generate an
image that I might use that supports
that type of post seems like there's an
issue however I can visualize the
concept okay great can you make me an
image of this as close as possible to
what you can create it has trouble
making like medical images so it has to
kind of it has a trust has a safety
layer currently I'm unable to generate
an image directly okay um can you make
something that you can
generate an image of similar to this
let's try this one more time I find it
very interesting that it's not creating
one because it has an algorithm to do
this built into it
um sometimes you just have to ask it
three or four times to do the thing that
it says that it can't
do and and that's another piece of adice
advice for AI is that if it tells you I
can't do it ask it okay we'll figure out
how you can do it that would be rude to
tell a person to do but with AI you can
actually start to kind of learn some of
this figure that out that's very
interesting how it it uh it showed I
mean that it illustrates what we're
talking about perfectly
okay now I want to
create a webinar about this for coaches
and course course creators and how AI
can help them with this by combining all
the ideas above okay so what I'm doing
is I'm just talking to it like a person
and I usually will say stuff out loud as
well as far as that goes so this could
be like you know what would the what
would the webinar be can you write some
sales copy for a landing page lead
magnet for this
webinar that I can Market with Facebook
ads to grow my email
list oh look at that it's creating an
email news newsletter it's creating uh
social media post let's ask it to do
this headline unlock your brain's hidden
potential discover how to use Ai and the
r Ras to Skyrocket your coaching
business are you a coach who's
struggling to stay focused and organized
you want to harness the power of AI to
elevate your business learn more about
yeah so that's a little bit all over the
place let's focus let's focus more on
productivity
and time management only in the sales
letter okay so I'm going to tell it to
kind of focus on that uh process for
transform your productivity using Ai and
the RAS you can boost your productivity
have effective time management
understand how the r Ras can make you
more productive
perfect so again this isn't necessarily
where we're kind of going with this I
actually developed a document called the
chat GPT prompt document it's over at my
website over at jeremi .c it's a Google
document that you can actually download
that has a number of my favorite prompts
that I use when I'm using AI you can go
find it right here the free chat GPT
prompt download and we've used a lot of
these prompts to to make eight figures
in our business and you can go grab this
right here as well okay and and ones
that I like is you can actually help
identify pain points and it can start to
um really dive deeper into the emotion
that we're experiencing ing when it
comes to who we're trying to reach so
this would be reached for somebody who's
overwhelmed they have distraction they
have poor time management they're
struggling with time commitment Miss
deadlines work life balance how many of
you deal with that how many of you
struggle with that as far as in your own
business okay it maybe if I hosted a
webinar on this topic some of you would
attend for example as far as that goes
transform your productivity with time
management in our free webinar and by
the way some of the stuff that we
literally just looked up that I showed
you could actually help help you with
that you could almost treat this as like
a reverse
webinar where I showed you kind of what
the content would be and then we
reversed it into some marketing
materials and you could do that for any
of your offers as far as that goes uh
using using AI one of my favorite
promises right here is the storytelling
salesletter
framework I tell it to kind of turn all
of that into a story format are you
tired of juggling endless tasks never
feeling like there's enough time in the
day I get it trying to balance business
business family and personal goals I
remember when my to-do list was like a
mountain I could never climb and was
constantly stressed and overwhelmed
imagine waking up knowing what you need
to do staying focused and finishing
tasks
efficiently and so this can obviously
help you write that I we also have it
where you can write it in the Sandy
Kowski tone Sandy Kowski that's my mom's
name she and I work together and we
wrote a lot of sales copy in our
business that we built to over $20
million a year in profit and so the AI
algorithm is actually trained on a lot
of the work that we did over the last
over the last 15 plus years are you
feeling overwhelmed with never ending
to-do list I totally get it I've been in
your shoes let me share a quick story
with you there was a time in my days
were filled with chaos yep so this helps
you really start to like write out your
marketing materials create a lot of
those things generate me some names for
this free lead magnet webinar this might
be a name that we might call it we might
use it create a little poster on canva
and Market it how to master your time
work smarter not harder time management
using AI um time is on your side and
ultimately the goal would be ultimate
ultimately this goal would be to make
more money as a business owner and get
more done please adjust based on this
adjusting based on what your target
client actually wants will be important
and this is where we get to steer the AI
like you're steering a car just like
with this steering wheel right here if I
took this steering wheel and we were
steering a car back and
forth you do the same thing with the AI
you're going to move it left or to the
right to decide which direction to take
it and that's one of the things I think
as well a lot of people don't do is they
don't correct it they don't correct the
ai's outputs they don't tell it
different things to get it to optimize
things better get more done and make
more money how Ai and the reticular
activating system can help entrepreneurs
unlock your earning potential boo
Revenue boosting time management tools
perfect so these are different ideas
that you could use on how to use AI to
help you succeed in your business or in
your life now check this out here's one
of the last prompts that I want to show
you and I'm going to sit down for this
and then I'm going to show you some of
the more advanced uh ways that you can
use AI as well that I like to use is um
brainstorm 20 possible unique questions
to dive deeper into other topics related
to the above
what are the key benefits of using AI
how can an entrepreneur integrate them
into their daily life what are real
world
examples okay and so what I can do is I
can take all these
questions copy them and then I'll edit
this one and delete where it asks the
questions and I'll tell it please answer
all of these questions in detail
and it will start answering the
questions how it can work how it can
help let's try this can you brainstorm
some unique ways the ra can be used to
help business owners that we have
discussed at all
above enhanced networking opportunities
helps you identify who to network with
improving created problem
solving leveraging it to enhance their
problem solving optimizing Learning and
Development enhanced customer insights
you'll recognize subtle patterns and
Trends in your customer Behavior
boosting team collaboration identifying
Market opportunities improving
negotiation skills by focusing on the
key out objectives and desired outcomes
it's very very true exactly that's
awesome even in Psychology today there's
a is there a link maybe there's not okay
so this is where we can use AI to kind
of find different answers as far as that
goes I really like
um this right
here about about recognize and this is
where a lot of people say oh they pray
and things like that prayer is a way to
activate the RIS as well even stronger
because then you're also having like a
spiritual awakening aspect to it can you
explain this how the
Neuroscience differs from prayer and
spir
[Music]
spirituality this is be very interesting
explanation um it's a network of neurons
in the brain stem that plays Central to
arousal and Consciousness what primary
functions is to vastly um filter out
vast amounts of sensory information
allowing only pertinent stuff to appear
so that it's filtering out information
as far as that goes Neuroscience versus
prayer and spirituality the Neuroscience
explanation is it's a physiological
thing studies show that goal setting
helps activate that in parent
spirituality the process of setting
intention and visualizing outcome can
lead to a perceived benefit the
mechanism is often attributed to divine
intervention while less empirical
directly linking spirituality to
specific specific neuro processes have
shown that prayer meditation can often
lead to better mental health well-being
less stress and then this benefits to a
combination of psychological social and
spiritual factors Effectiveness and
attributed
um me see approach so there's that um is
there is there some ways that
spiritually and the
interconnectedness of all humans this
comes together together as well into
this with the RAS to bring to familiar
entangled people together so again this
is something that might combine a little
bit of spirituality some quantum physics
as far as that goes okay both spiritual
practice and the ARs emphasize the power
of intention it might visualize a
meeting Collective Consciousness in
group meditation the collective can
amplify individual intentions they'll
activate things more powerfully in the
group so that so that's exactly what
happens other people might also be
praying for the same thing and then that
creates a lot of heightened awareness
and synchronicities as well as there's
energy and vibration right here
spiritual beliefs the concept of energy
and vibrations that attract each
other as far as that goes okay um how
does this play into tradition because
for me I'm a Christian traditional uh
Christian faith beliefs or even uh
Judaism as far as this goes you know
Judaism even even in in other faiths as
well uh emphasize the power of prayer
intention focus and divine guidance
these principles line a well with
scientific understanding of the RAS
prayer means you're communicating with
God expressing desire seeking guidance
aligning one with God's purpose when we
pray with a specific intention it does
it does it primes the RIS to filter out
things that don't fit into what's align
with their prayer that's great I love
that faith and
expectancy uh directing one's heart and
mind towards God and sincerity so this
all kind of comes
together and and I'm like I'm learning
different stuff even right here that's
like a really really cool conversation
that you can have on this whole topic
and the AI is helping us navigate this
by brainstorming something I hadn't even
thought of is how the RAS actually helps
us with our networking I notice it
happens all the time I end up running
into people because I set an intention I
notice certain people that are standing
out when I want to talk with them versus
if I'm closed off I don't want to be
bothered things like that I start
pushing away and our body language even
starts to do things like that as far as
that goes even when we're doing webinars
even when we're marketing ourselves it
happens that way okay and so this can
help us learn this type of stuff as far
as this goes and when you can learn how
to use AI in a way that really truly
helps you activate your brain helps you
come up with ideas for your marketing
and helps you really do and accomplish
things that you necessarily wouldn't
come up with on your own or would have
taken you hours of reading through books
and articles and stuff like that we were
able to literally research and come up
with and formulate some incredible ideas
just in about 30 minutes as far as this
goes now a couple tools that I like as
well that are out there there's other AI
algorithms that you can pay for um
Google Gemini Advanced is one of
them I find it to be pretty cool as far
as how it explains a lot of different
concepts I have an account with Gemini
Advanced you can actually get it for
free for two months and use their 1.5
million pro model with a 1 million
context window which is just incredible
as far as what this gives you to be able
to kind of get access with that you can
even also code um you can write code and
create apps and do all kinds of crazy
stuff with this as far as this goes so
like if I click on Gemini Advanced right
here I have Gemini Advanced loaded up
right here and what I might do is I
might just go back and I might copy all
of what this has generated I'm going to
copy all of this text we're going to go
all the way to the top
here we're going to have it read through
all of this stuff right here
and I'm going to ask
it brainstorm 20 additional questions to
ask the person who created the following
dissertation that are not included or
talked about in this algorithm and this
is where we can actually um we're going
to say it's a
dissertation I'm going to paste all of
the stuff from the other one one
here oh you know what it didn't paste
everything we're going to put it into a
text document is what we have to do so
I'm going to say that this is the
dissertation I'm going to save this as a
text document to my
computer and then we're going to import
this as a data
file Brin 20 additional questions to ask
this person who created the following
dissertation so it's analyzing it it's
working on the response what inspired
you to choose a specific topic for your
dissertation practical
applications um
what inspired you I was inspired to
explore this due to its profound impact
one challenge is finding complete compal
data linking it to things it's amazing
so this helps you unpack new and
exciting ideas as far as this
goes based on this text document can you
brainstorm other ideas and ways that the
RAS can be
used it's analyzing the do document it's
going to come up with this based on
what's written
there enhancing intuition in decision-
making improved memory and
recall overcoming procrastination
becoming resilient and adaptable
improving public speaking skills
yep and So based on this you can use
another algorithm to ask questions about
about the other algorithm as far as that
goes we could even start a new
conversation what are some ways to use
AI in a coaching business we can see
what kind of outputs this gives us it's
a powerful tool enhancing client
interactions personalized insights chat
Bots virtual assistance sentiment
analysis I use that a
lot generating in content video editing
AI powered coaching platforms
gamification yep so this is even topics
that weren't even discussed with chat
gbt that Google Gemini came out with so
different algorithms different AI
algorithms have different outputs
there's another one called cloud
claw. a it's right here this is another
one and they have a free version as well
as a paid one the the paid one is the
the better one um it's called
Opus and you can do a lot with that I
like to use po.com so po.com has access
to all of these different ones right
here
okay and so what we can do is you can
either create images I had it like I I
told it uh generate me an image of a
beautiful Latin model woman and it
created this image right here I was
testing out this realistic Vision
Generation image model right here uh
make me an image of her at a restaurant
with a date as far as this goes and you
can literally then start to like build
out scenes and things like that based on
what it created and stuff like that so
it's very interesting how you can even
use this as far as that goes you can use
um stable diffusion to be able to do
things like this there we go oh that's
cool it's a great photo so again you can
use um these algorithms that make
different
imagery different graphics for different
things as far as this goes awesome that
looks pretty cool uh you can ask
questions right here Mistral
medium is
a uh it's another algorithm it's an open
source one I was researching about
dopamine you can explore the different
algorithms you can use GPT 40 Gemini 1.5
Pro Cloud Opus uh image
Generation Um I can use mistol I can use
llama this is from meta as far as this
goes um what is the fastest way to
prime your
Ras I could also ask uh real
viz make me a graphic of
someone priming their Ras
that's
interesting somebody painting something
with let's try
this it's very
fast so it's doing it like a like a like
a I mean
reticular
activating
system oh so it explains kind of how how
that work that's interesting okay so
anyways po allows you to use all these
different algorithms and so you could
quickly ask the same question of
multiple different AIS to see what kind
of outputs it gives you to one answer or
another so you'll get a different answer
from each one but then you can kind of
compile all this information together
and truly start to learn a lot of things
fast create marketing materials really
quickly and things like that by using a
variety of algorithms using the PO
platform which is really cool so PO is
really cool I give access to it to the
people that are on my team they use it
to generate a lot of different graphics
and images and things like that even you
can use it for stock images generate me
this is one uh generate me an image of
of a woman at her computer a a beautiful
Italian woman working on her Graphics
design in her home office
right here you go guess she's Italian
but it's like a stock image can you make
her
happy I don't want her to be sad oh
that's interesting okay um
um let's copy this make her happy with
her
work and these are really fast as far as
how they generate these there you go
there's one she looks
decently somewhat happy meta has a
platform too that you can use called
meta AI now this one's free if you have
a Facebook account you can use meta Ai
and you can generate different images
and graphics and things like that as far
as this goes which is really really cool
so I can tell it generate me um an image
of a woman working at the desk of her
computer and it's going to generate me
four variations that then we can
use um right here this one's good
perfect uh we can edit it we can say can
you put her in a pink shirt and it will
literally take the image and it'll
change it based on my request
as far as this
goes okay not quite the same person but
there we go um can you have her eating
Chinese food as
well and so you can use even meta AI to
generate like really cool images it's
trained on Instagram and Facebook images
is what it is there we go that's a cool
it's a very interesting image it it
looks kind of like a like a like a night
in the office or like my wife used to
work on graphics and stuff like that so
anyways those are those are just some
really great ways to use AI that you can
use to play around to come up with
different ideas to do different levels
of research stuff like that uh there's
one other AI that I love called
perplexity doai and perplexity doai does
research with you as far as this
goes uh such as can
you research why Chinese food is so
addictive I mean it is you eat enough of
it you want more why do you crave it
more and it'll find citations and
sources and then give you the reasons
why a lot of this oh a lot of this a lot
of the uh sauces have sugar in them yeah
flavor enhancers high fat content yep
that's it and it gives sources and
things like that you can have it uh
rewrite stuff based
on uh you know various algorithms you
can pay for the upgraded version of
of uh perplexity Pro which is really
really cool so you can have it search
for videos it can find videos why is
junk food junk food addiction killing us
let's see that's a study on China this
one is about junk food this one's about
addictive properties and alra Ultra
processed foods how does what we eat
affect our brain things like that and so
it's really kind of cool how you can use
AI to really do a lot of research to
find different topics and to dive deeper
into giving you various ideas now one of
the other ways that I love to use AI as
well is that you can even take YouTube
videos and you can paste them into
Gemini on Google and it will answer
questions based on the YouTube video you
can find a transcript from any videos
that are on YouTube and you can copy
that transcript into chat GPT and start
asking it questions about the topic or
you can have it reformulate an idea from
a video that you found on YouTube into
another topic and help you generate and
come up with new ideas that you could
create for various things that you're
doing so we get to really kind of bring
together a lot of ideas to create a lot
of things to get very creative again we
don't want to plagiarize other people's
ideas but using them as inspiration to
inspire your brain and to go on a
journey with the AI is very powerful and
very fun and this is something that I
Mentor my clients in and we work with
them on and I work with my clients
through in my client growth acceler
program as we show you how to grow your
business how to use AI in a way that
doesn't lose your integrity or your
reputation or your voice so that it
sounds like you and so that you can
actually start to make money in a
business so that you're not struggling
wondering is this going to work do what
do I need to do you get access to me and
my experience of building businesses
online for over 21 years in the space of
online marketing in the space of coaches
and course creators authors speakers and
helping them how do you run your Live
Events how do you get people to show up
to those events how do you generate more
leads for your business how do you run
your Facebook ads these are various
things that we help Mentor people on and
so I would encourage you to go over to
my website jump on the waiting list for
my client growth accelerator when we
open the doors to that next I'd love to
have you jump into that with us and be a
part of our community to grow together
with us and to start to brainstorm
different ways for you to be able to
actually reach your goals online we'll
talk soon have a going everybody body